a focused on my bar and you want to order a
Mediterranean breakfast
what you have to do is read what
comes on the screen, no matter reading it
in your head, you don't have to read it out
loud, okay, that way you can practice and that way I don't look like an
idiot, sometimes you'll be able to choose between
two options, option a, option b,
you decide, let's start, welcome, what would you like? Would you like to have?
[Music]
no, we don't have Colombian coffee, we have
other blends, if you don't mind the flavor,
you are a customer with very
exquisite taste. You only drink Colombian coffee,
very good, a cola cao
and something else,
okay, and a croissant, a heart.
I think we're out of
croissants, we don't have any more.
Let me let me confirm it for a second, we don't have any
croissants left.
No,
okay, thank you. No,
the cross sans is gone, okay,
then would you like a cola cao and
toast with tomato?
That would be all
very well, do
n't worry, it won't take long, as you can
see, we don't have many customers today,
which is a bit strange because on Tuesday
mornings we are usually packed.
If you don't know what it's like to feel, this
is to feel very good.
I'll bring it to you right away in a cafeteria or a bar normally they give you the cola cao in a sachet and you pour it yourself but let me tell you something a secret really we're not in a bar we're at home and I don't have a cola cao in a sachet
okay
here it is cola cao and toast with
tomato
although in this case it's with
tomato because there's only one
yes there should be one on each table
here you have
[Music]
and tell me
the bill if right now you prefer to pay
by card or in cash
with card okay just a moment while I go get
the POS
thank you just
a moment it
seems like it's not working can you
enter your pin it's
not working I'll
try one more time it
seems like you have to pay in cash
here's your change thank you very much
have a nice day see you
later I hope you liked
this video and if you want me to make more
like this let me know in a comment and that's it
and now I can finally
eat my toast which is harder than
a rock because it's been waiting here for half an hour half an hour it
needs salt